So before we simulate a
failure let's
Make sure everything is working
very
Well first let's make sure the
application is healthy before we
Simulate any
Problem so let me put the
I read the name so as we can see
here the status is healthy
Service holder API and the dev
and so it's working very
Well as you can see the
application is healthy and
Responding
successfully the status is
Healthy service orders
API everything is working
Well now let's make sure
cloud watch isn't reporting any
problem
Yet so it's okay so
The alarm is in the okay state
exactly what we would like
Expect before triggering the
Demo and finally let's confirm
if the ECS service itself is
Healthy so as we can see here is
the status is active for the
ECS service so our container is
working also very well so
At this point everything looks
good the application is
Healthy the ECS service is
running correctly and
CloudWatch isn't detecting any
issue now let's intentionally
Break the application and watch
how the the platform detects the
Problem so analyze it with
AI and so we will begin the
remediation work